Guide to the Stanford University, Office of Vice President and General Counsel, Records SC0178
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, 1963-1977; Series 11
  - Government relations, 1967-1976; Subseries 4
    - Meyer Library - Student Monitor Program, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Placement Services Policy (COSS), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Political activities on/from campus community, policy, 1967-1976 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - President's Office, 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Privacy act, 1963-1976; Subseries 5
    - Administrative Panel/Human Subjects Research. Folder #1, 1971-1976 (Box 14, Folder 16Administrative Panel/Human Subjects Research. Folder #)
    - Administrative Panel/Human Subjects Research. Folder #2, 1971-1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Administrative Panel/Privacy of Information, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Administrative Panel/Privacy of Information, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      Inc. some Minutes.
    - California Fair Information Practices, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Human Subjects Guidelines, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Human Subjects Research/Contracts, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Human Subjects Research/Contracts, 1976 Jan-Feb (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Human Subjects Research/Contracts, 1976 Mar-Jun (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Human Subjects/Research Liability, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Public Events, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Recombinant DNA, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Recordings in Sound, Stanford Program for, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Restricted Gifts, 1972-1974 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Signature Resolutions, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Solar Energy Research Institute (SERI), General. Folder #1, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Solar Energy Research Institute (SERI), General. Folder #2, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Solar Energy Research Institute (SERI), General. Folder #3, 1976 (Item 15, Folder 3)
    - Solar Energy Research Institute - Proposal. Folder #1, 1976 Jul 15 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Solar Energy Research Institute - Proposal. Folder #2, 1976 Jul 15 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Solar Energy Research Institute - Request for Proposals (RFP), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Stanford Campus Recreation Association, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Synchroton Radiation Project, 1963-1973 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Students - Judicial Procedure. Folder #1, 1968-1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Students - Judicial Procedure. Folder #2, 1968-1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Suits, 1970-1976; Subseries 6
    General
    See also Boxes 16 - 18.
    - Bazile & Laury Case, San Mateo Superior Court, 1971 May 2 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - General, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Hukari et al. Folder #1, 1970-1972 (Item 15, Folder 13)
    - Hukari et al. Folder #2, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Medical School Grievance - Selliken, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Mosquito Abatement District vs. Jasper Ridge Marshes, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - NAACP vs. Stanford University re. Frenchman's Terrace, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Richard s vs. Stanford, 1973 Jan (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Stanford University and Stanford Union of Research Physicists Folder #1, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Stanford University and Stanford Union of Research Physicists Folder #2, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - United Nations Conference, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - University relations, 1963-1977; Subseries 7
    - Brigham Young University, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Cable Television, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1969-1975 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Use of the Stanford Name, 1963-1977 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Use of Swimming Pools, 1972-1973 (Item 15, Folder 26)
    - Zaire Student Kidnapping - General. Folder #1, 1975 May 19 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Zaire Student Kidnapping - General. Folder #2, 1975 May 19 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Zaire Student Kidnapping - Newsclippings, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Special legal matters, 1969-1976; Subseries 8
    See also Suits, Box 15.
    - Affidavits, general, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Affidavits, general, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Affidavits, research, 1976 (Item 16, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Alexander, vs. Educational Testing Service, et al., 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Coyote Hills Suit, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Cranston Amendment, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Cross vs. Stanford University - correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Cross vs. Stanford University - litigation file. Folder #1, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Cross vs. Stanford University - litigation file. Folder #2, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Dillingham Land Corp. Lease, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, Stanford vs., pleadings, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Furumoto, Lee and Ho Suit - pleadings, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Injunction (Stanford vs. Alhadeff et al.), folder #1, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Injunction (Stanford vs. Alhadeff et al.), folder #2, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Injunction (Busse vs. Palo Alto Red Squad), - Affidavits in support of complaint, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Injunction (Busse vs. Palo Alto Red Squad) - General material, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Injunction (Stanford vs. Barkley et al.) - Affidavits in support of. Includes photos, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Injunction (Stanford vs. Barkley et al.) - Counter-affidavits, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Injunction (Stanford vs. Barkley et al.) - Preliminary injunction, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Injunction (Stanford vs. Barkley et al.) - Pleadings. Folder #1, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Injunction (Stanford vs. Barkley et al.) - Pleadings. Folder #2, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - I.R.S. - American WiIdlife Leadership Foundation (AWLF) et al. Folder #1, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - I.R.S. - American WiIdlife Leadership Foundation (AWLF) et al. Folder #2, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - I.R.S. audit, 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Maichel, Karol - Pleadings. Folder #1, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Maichel, Karol - Pleadings. Folder #2, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - McGill, Roscoe vs. Stanford, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - National Labor Relations Board, 1971-1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - National Labor Relations Board - Stanford brief, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - PHEEA (Pa. Higher Education Assistance Agency) - Haverford et al., 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Rauch litigation. Folder #1, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Rauch litigation. Folder #2, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Rauch litigation. Folder #3, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - So. California shareholders suit, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - The Stanford Daily vs. Zurcher et al., 1972 Oct 5 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Testcor, Inc. vs. Stanford University, Stanford Press. Folder #1, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Testcor, Inc. vs. Stanford University, Stanford Press. Folder #2, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - United Stanford Employees, Stanford vs. Folder #1, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - United Stanford Employees, Stanford vs. Folder #2, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - H. Bruce Franklin, 1971-1975; Subseries 9
    - Advisory Board meeting, 1971 Oct 20 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Brief, 1971 Nov (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Brief, supplementary, 1971 Dec (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Charges, statement of, 1971 Mar 22 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence. Folder #1, 1971-1975 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence. Folder #2, 1971-1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence. Folder #3, 1971-1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence. Folder #4, 1971-1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with Trustees and special meeting, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Decision, 1972 Jan 5 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Depositions. Folder #1, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11Depositions. Folder #)
    - Depositions. Folder #2, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Depositions. Folder #3, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Drafts file, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Expenses, etc., 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Injunction proceedings, 1971 (Item 18, Folder 16)
    - Interrogatories. Folder #1, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Interrogatories. Folder #2, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Lodge disruption, 1971 Jan 11 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Motion for Reconsideration. Folder #1, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Motion for Reconsideration. Folder #2, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Pleadings file. Folder #1, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Pleadings file. Folder #2, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Pleadings file. Folder #3, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Pleadings file. Folder #1, 1972 Aug (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Pleadings file. Folder #2, 1972 Aug (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Pleadings file. Folder #3, 1972 Aug (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Pleadings file. Folder #4, 1972 Aug (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Pleadings file. Folder #1, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Pleadings file. Folder #2, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Publicity and news clippings. Folder #1, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Publicity and news clippings. Folder #2, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Publicity and news clippings. Folder #3, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Publicity and news clippings, post-Advisory Board decision. Folder #1, 1972 Jan (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Publicity and news clippings, post-Advisory Board decision. Folder #2, 1972 Jan (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Tape transcriptions, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Witness file. Folder #1, 1971 Apr 8 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Witness file. Folder #2, 1971 Apr 8 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Working papers, Advisory Board, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 4 (Vol.))
  - Audio recordings, 1971-1972; Subseries 10
    - Lodge incident, 1971 Jan 11; 21.1; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 21)
    - Case #65, SJC, 1971 Feb 12; 21.2; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 21)
    - Case #65, SJC, 1971 Feb 18; 21.3; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 21)
    - Richard W. Lyman interview on KZSU (re-broadcast 4/13/71), 1971 Apr 11; 21.4; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 21)
    - Art Auditorium, 1971 Apr 20; 21.5; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 21)
    - Cubberley meeting, 1972 Apr 17; 21.6; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 21)
    - Interviews, 1971 Mar 9; 21.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
    - Interviews, 1971 Mar 9; 21.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
    - Interviews, 1971 Mar 9; 21.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
    - Medical Center, 1971 Apr 14; 21.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
    - Medical Center, 1971 Apr 14; 21.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
    - Hospital, 1971 Apr 14; 21.12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)
    - Old Union sit-in; Faculty Club sit-in, 1972 Jan 24; 21.13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 21)